Are you ready, kids?
孩子们，你们准备好了吗？
Kids: Aye, aye, Captain.
孩子们：是的，是的，队长。
I can't  hear  you.
我听不到你说话。
Kids:   Aye, aye,
Captain!
孩子们：是啊是啊
队长！
Captain: ♪ Ohh... ♪
队长：♪ 哦...♪
♪ Who lives in a pineapple
under the sea? ♪
♪ 谁住在菠萝里
在海底？ ♪
Kids: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
孩子们：♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ Absorbent and yellow
and porous is he ♪
队长：♪ 吸水性的，黄色的
他是多孔的 ♪
Kids: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
孩子们：♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ If nautical nonsense
be somethin' you wish ♪
船长：♪ 如果是航海方面的废话
成为你所希望的那样 ♪
Kids: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
孩子们：♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ Then drop on the deck
and flop like a fish ♪
船长：♪ 然后降落在甲板上
然后像鱼一样扑通扑通♪
Kids: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
孩子们：♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ Ready? ♪
队长：♪ 准备好了吗？ ♪
All: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
全部： ♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ SpongeBob
SquarePants ♪
队长：♪ 海绵宝宝
方裤♪
Man: Ohh...
男：哦……
I just can't decide
what to order.
我就是无法决定
订购什么。
You already ordered.
你已经订购了。
Don't rush me, young lady!
别催我，年轻的女士！
Hurry up, SpongeBob!
快点，海绵宝宝！
What is taking you so long?
是什么让你花了这么长时间？
I'm adding the love.
我正在添加爱。
You're not being  paid  to love.
付钱给你不是为了爱。
I'm not in it for the money.
我不是为了钱。
I'll always treasure
this time we've had together.
我会永远珍惜
这次我们在一起了。
Look!
看！
SpongeBob: Aww...
海绵宝宝：哇……
Well, I'll be cooked in butter.
好吧，我会用黄油煮。
It's Jim, me original fry cook.
我是吉姆，我原来的油炸厨师。
Krabs!
螃蟹们！
The  Jim?
吉姆？
He-Who-Flipped-Krabby-Patties
in The Before Time?
他翻转蟹肉饼
在之前的时间？
You're doing well, Jim.
你做得很好，吉姆。
Is, is, is that limo solid gold?
是、是、那辆豪华轿车是纯金的吗？
It sure is.
确实如此。
I was on my way
to my solid gold mansion
next to my solid gold lake
我正在路上
to my solid gold mansion
next to my solid gold lake
when I thought I'd take
a little trip down memory lane.
当我以为我会采取
沿着记忆的小路走一趟。
Good old Jim.
好老吉姆。
When you worked here,
the place had class.
当你在这里工作时，
这个地方有课。
Yeah, when this place
had class...
是的，当这个地方
上课了...
we've had some great times, too,
right, Squidward?
我们也度过了一段美好的时光
对吧，章鱼哥？
No.
不。
Hey, that's new.
嘿，这是新的。
Employee of the month, huh?
本月最佳员工吧？
That's me!
这就是我！
Krabs: Don't worry, Jim.
蟹老板：别担心，吉姆。
No one could ever
take your place.
从来没有人能够
取代你的位置。
The original
is still underneath.
原来的
还在下面。
your "Best Employee Ever" award.
您的“最佳员工”奖。
SpongeBob, sweep up this mess
while Jim and I catch up.
海绵宝宝，清理这个烂摊子
吉姆和我迎头赶上。
Yes, sir.
是的，先生。
After I left the Krusty Krab,
I worked at some of the finest
restaurants around the world.
当我离开蟹堡王后
我曾在一些最优秀的公司工作过
世界各地的餐厅。
I got so successful,
I was able to retire in luxury.
我如此成功，
我能够奢侈地退休。
Would you sign my Krabby Patty?
你愿意签下我的蟹黄派吗？
Oh, I don't sign
what I didn't make.
哦，我不签
我没有做的。
Hey, big shot, why don't you
step behind the fryer,
for old time's sake?
嘿，大佬，你为什么不呢？
走到油炸锅后面，
为了旧时光？
You're on, Krabs.
蟹蟹，你来了。
But I'll have to charge you.
但我得向你收费。
Oh, oh, you always knew
how to make me laugh.
哦，哦，你一直都知道
如何让我笑。
You just don't find employees
like that anymore.
你只是找不到员工
不再这样了。
Yeah, not unless you looked
right in front of you!
是的，除非你看
I appreciate you, Squidward.
我很感激你，章鱼哥。
Now I feel complete.
现在我感觉很完整。
Now how's about that Patty?
现在帕蒂怎么样了？
Everyone, watch and learn.
大家一起来观看、学习吧。
No one watches Jim.
没有人看吉姆。
One Patty, the  right  way.
一个帕蒂，正确的方式。
it's a thing of beauty.
这是一件美丽的事情。
What's so great
about a Jim Patty, anyway?
有什么了不起
无论如何，关于吉姆·帕蒂？
Eh, it's O.K.
呃，没关系。
Wow...
哇...
That was...  amazing.
那真是……太棒了。
Um, Mr. Jim, sir?
嗯，吉姆先生，先​​生？
Oh, hey... You.
哦，嘿...你。
You're the...
Guy who sweeps up, right?
你是那个...
扫地的家伙，对吗？
I'm the new fry cook, sir.
先生，我是新来的炒菜厨师。
Oh.
哦。
You made that stepped-on thing
I saw earlier, right?
你创造了那个被踩到的东西
我很早就看到了，对吧？
Do you have any tips
you could pass on to a rookie?
你有什么建议吗
你可以传授给新人吗？
Hmm, besides
don't step on the food?
嗯，除此之外
不要踩到食物吗？
Please critique my work!
请批评我的作品！
I wish to learn
at the feet of the master!
我想学习
在主人脚下！
Now that's the way to grovel.
现在这就是卑躬屈膝的方式。
Jim: I'll do it.
吉姆：我会做的。
Yep, pickle slices
were too thick.
是的，泡菜片
太厚了。
Hold it...
坚持住...
Hold it.
握住它。
O.K.
好的。
Nope, too much mustard, see?
不，芥末太多了，明白吗？
Aw, man,
噢，伙计，
Am I a fraud?
我是骗子吗？
SpongeBob, what are you
doing in there?
海绵宝宝，你是什么
在那里做什么？
Crying my eyes out.
哭得我眼睛都肿了。
Well, hurry up,
I gotta cry, too.
嗯，快点，
我也得哭了
Why, Squidward?
为什么，章鱼哥？
Because when Jim leaves,
I'll be stuck with  you  again.
因为当吉姆离开时
我会再次和你纠缠在一起。
Don't worry Squidward.
别担心，章鱼哥。
Jim won't be leaving.
吉姆不会离开。
He's taking my job.
他抢走了我的工作。
I'm the one who's leaving.
我就是那个要离开的人。
Really?
真的吗？
Yes!
是的！
Hot-cha-cha, hot-cha-cha,
hot-cha-cha-cha-cha-cha-cha!
热恰恰，热恰恰，
热恰恰！
Ooh!
哦！
The Krusty Krab deserves better
than my meager skills.
蟹堡王值得更好的
比我微薄的技能。
I should be professional.
我应该是专业的。
I must... resign.
我必须……辞职。
"Dear Mr. Krabs..."
“亲爱的蟹老板……”
Krabs: Three cheers for
the world's greatest fry cook!
蟹蟹：欢呼三声
世界上最伟大的油炸厨师！
SpongeBob!
海绵宝宝！
Come here,
help us cheer for Jim.
来这里，
帮助我们为吉姆加油。
Hip, hip...
臀，臀……
All: Hooray!
全体：万岁！
Hip, hip...
臀，臀……
Hooray!
万岁！
Krabs: Hip, hip...
螃蟹：嘻嘻，嘻嘻……
All: Hooray!
全体：万岁！
Good-bye, grill.
再见，烧烤。
Good-bye, pot.
Good-bye, pan.
再见，锅。
再见，潘。
So long, fry fat.
这么久了，炒脂肪。
Good-bye, grease stain.
再见，油渍。
Good-bye,
frozen patty number one.
再见，
冷冻肉饼排名第一。
Good-bye,
frozen patty number two.
再见，
二号冷冻肉饼。
Narrator: 298 frozen patties
later...
旁白：298块冷冻肉饼
后来...
Good-bye, freezer.
再见，冰箱。
Krabs: SpongeBob?
蟹蟹：海绵宝宝？
SpongeBob?
海绵宝宝？
That smells like
a resignation letter.
闻起来像
辞职信。
SpongeBob's resignation!
海绵宝宝辞职了！
Oh, this is terrible.
哦，这太可怕了。
No one's making patties.
没有人做馅饼。
And that means
I'm not making money!
这意味着
我不赚钱！
Hey, Eugene, where's that
little fry cook of yours?
嘿，尤金，那是哪里
你家的小厨师吗？
He thinks you're taking his job,
so he's run off.
他认为你抢走了他的工作
所以他逃跑了。
Hey, great idea,
and you can give me a raise.
嘿，好主意，
你可以给我加薪。
SpongeBob: Look at them.
海绵宝宝：看看他们。
Mr. Krabs is probably offering
Jim my job right now.
蟹老板可能会提供
吉姆现在是我的工作。
Well, I better go find him.
好吧，我最好去找他。
SpongeBob?
海绵宝宝？
Don't worry, Mr. Krabs,
I was just leaving.
别担心，蟹老板，
我正要离开。
I'm not fit to inhabit
the same kitchen as Jim.
我不适合居住
和吉姆同一个厨房。
So it is with a heavy heart
that I relinquish my position
as fry cook.
所以心情沉重
我放弃我的立场
作为炒菜。
What are you
thinking, SpongeBob?
你是什么
海绵宝宝在想吗？
I'm not taking your job.
我不会抢你的工作。
But you're the greatest fry cook
in the world.
但你是最棒的炒菜厨师
在世界上。
The Krusty Krab
deserves better than me.
蟹堡王
值得比我更好。
Both those statements
are true, SpongeBob.
这两种说法
是真的，海绵宝宝。
But there's a reason why
I left the Krusty Krab.
但有一个原因
我离开了蟹堡王。
It all started
on a warm summer evening.
一切都开始了
在一个温暖的夏日傍晚。
Jim: Business was slow
吉姆：业务进展缓慢
so Squidward and I were having
one of our famous bull sessions.
所以章鱼哥和我在一起
我们著名的牛市之一。
We should open
our own restaurant and stop
lining old man K's pockets.
我们应该打开
我们自己的餐厅和车站
衬在老K的口袋里。
No, thanks.
不，谢谢。
I'm just doing this until
my clarinet career takes off.
我只是这样做直到
我的单簧管事业起飞了。
What if it never does?
如果它永远不会发生怎么办？
Don't you want to have something
to fall back on?
你不想拥有一些东西吗
依靠？
Yeah, ha!
是啊，哈！
I could lose my beautiful
flowing hair too, but I'm not
buying a wig yet.
我可能会失去我的美丽
头发也飘逸，但我不是
还没买假发呢。
Well, while you go wig shopping,
I'm gonna go talk to Mr. Krabs.
好吧，当你去买假发时，
我要去跟蟹老板谈谈
Hey, Mr. Krabs.
嘿，蟹老板。
You got a second?
你还有时间吗？
Anything for you,
Jimmy me boy.
为你做任何事，
吉米我的孩子。
Cop a squat and lay your racket.
深蹲并放下球拍。
Tell me what's on your wig, Jim.
告诉我你的假发上有什么，吉姆。
Cut the gas, Krabs,
and dig this.
关掉油门，螃蟹，
并挖掘这个。
I've been
busting my conch for you.
我去过
为你打破我的海螺。
You better lay on some
extra gravy, or I'm gonna
agitate the gravel.
你最好躺上一些
额外的肉汁，否则我会
搅拌砾石。
What now?
现在怎么办？
You know, lay a patch.
你知道，打个补丁。
Excuse me?
打扰一下？
Give me a raise or I'm quitting.
给我加薪，不然我就辞职。
A "raise"?
“加薪”？
Hmm, that's not
in my hiptionary.
嗯，那不是
在我的嘻哈词典中。
Help me get with it, Jack.
帮我解决这个问题，杰克。
Stop talking like that.
别再这样说话了。
These sideburns aren't real.
这些鬓角不是真的。
I need more money
in my paycheck at the end
of every week,  capisce?
我需要更多的钱
最后在我的薪水中
每周，capisce？
my hair,
my beautiful hair.
我的头发，
我美丽的头发。
Squidward: My hair, my hair.
章鱼哥：我的头发，我的头发。
Ah, it's still as funny today
as it was then.
啊今天还是一样搞笑
就像当时一样。
You see, SpongeBob.
你看，海绵宝宝。
You've got one quality
Jim will never have.
你有一种品质
吉姆永远不会。
You're cheap.
你很便宜。
Wow, I never thought of it
that way.
哇，我从来没想过
那样。
So you'll stay?
那么你会留下来吗？
Aye-aye, Mr. Krabs.
是的，蟹老板先生。
Then get to work, lad!
然后开始工作吧，小伙子！
Well, Eugene, looks like you've
got yourself another sucker.
嗯，尤金，看起来你已经
又给自己找了一个傻瓜。
The kid's a good fry cook
这孩子炒菜的手艺很好
but he'll only be
a great fry cook
但他只会
一位出色的炒菜厨师
when he finally
gets the guts to quit this dump.
当他终于
有勇气离开这个垃圾场。
Good luck, SpongeBob.
祝你好运，海绵宝宝。
You're gonna need it.
你会需要它。
The Krusty Krab isn't a dump.
蟹堡王不是垃圾场。
Oh, she's a dump, all right.
哦，她就是个废物，好吧。
But she's my dump.
但她是我的垃圾。
Oh...
哦...
SpongeBob: "And slowly,
ever so slowly
海绵宝宝：“慢慢地，
如此缓慢地
"the ancient crypt door
creaks open.
“古老的墓穴门
吱吱作响地打开了。
"And from the festering brine
of the darkest darkness
“从溃烂的盐水中
最黑暗的黑暗
"crawled forth monsters
of such vile nature
“怪物爬了出来
性质如此恶劣
"whose appearance was so
hideous and threatening
“谁的外表如此
可怕且具有威胁性
that the author  died
trying to recount them
in this novel!"
作者去世了
试图重述它们
在这本小说里！”
But it's only a story,
right, Gary?
但这只是一个故事，
对吧，加里？
Why don't you
sleep up here tonight, Gary?
你为什么不
今晚就睡在这里吗，加里？
Well, I guess I'll be
turning off the light now.
好吧，我想我会
现在关灯。
Sure is dark.
当然是黑暗了。
SpongeBob: Oh, it's just
a chair.
海绵宝宝：哦，只是
一把椅子。
I guess I'm imagining things
in the  dark.
我想我在想象一些事情
在黑暗中。
SpongeBob: Another monster!
海绵宝宝：又一个怪物！
Ah, it's just a coral branch.
啊，只是一根珊瑚树枝。
Nothing to be scared of.
没什么好害怕的。
Hey, Squidward,
have you seen SpongeBob?
嘿，章鱼哥，
你见过海绵宝宝吗？
Whoa.
哇哦。
You don't look so good, laddie.
你看起来不太好，小伙子。
Oh, it's nothing, Mr. Krabs.
哦，没什么，蟹老板。
I just had a rough night.
我刚刚度过了一个艰难的夜晚。
But it's nice and bright today.
但今天天气很好，很明亮。
Meanderin' mermaids.
蜿蜒的美人鱼。
What's all this racket, boy?
小伙子，这到底是怎么回事？
SpongeBob: Oh, oh, the dark!
海绵宝宝：噢，噢，黑暗！
Get it off, get it off,
get it off, get it off!
脱下来，脱下来，
脱下来，脱下来！
SpongeBob, get ahold
of yourself.
海绵宝宝，抱住
你自己。
What is it now, boy?
现在怎么样了，孩子？
Whenever I blink,
I see nothing but the darkness.
每当我眨眼的时候，
除了黑暗我什么也看不见。
Then don't blink.
那就别眨眼。
Brilliant idea, Mr. Krabs.
好主意，蟹老板。
Yes, it's working.
是的，它正在工作。
SpongeBob, that's enough!
海绵宝宝，够了！
We've got 50 orders to fill.
我们有 50 个订单需要完成。
Now go in the cooler
and get some fresh patties.
现在进入冷藏室
并买一些新鲜的肉饼。
SpongeBob: You want me
to go in...
海绵宝宝：你想要我
进去...
The darkness!
黑暗！
Now look, lad.
现在看，小伙子。
Your work is starting to
affect me profits.
你的工作开始了
影响我的利润。
You need to get yourself
some shuteye.
你需要让自己
闭上眼睛。
Why don't you go
get yourself a night light?
你为什么不走
给自己买一盏夜灯吗？
Night light?
夜灯？
Yeah, boy.
是的，男孩。
It'll keep your room lit
so you won't be scared stiff.
它会让你的房间保持明亮
这样你就不会被吓得僵硬。
Great idea, Mr. Krabs.
好主意，蟹老板。
Night lights... Night lights...
夜灯……夜灯……
It's beautiful.
很美丽。
Excuse me.
打扰一下。
Are these nightlights  guaranteed
这些夜灯有保证吗
to keep the creepy creatures
of the dark away?
来保留那些令人毛骨悚然的生物
黑暗的远去？
Now that I can see, whoo-hoo!
现在我能看到了，呼呼！
I can sleep.
我可以睡觉了。
I wonder what's in my dark,
scary-looking bathroom.
我想知道我的黑暗里有什么
看起来很吓人的浴室。
Night light, night light!
小夜灯，小夜灯！
Oh, thank you.
哦，谢谢。
Whew.
呼。
Oh, thank you.
哦，谢谢。
There, there, there, and there.
那里，那里，那里，还有那里。
I've been meaning to change
your tail light anyway, Gary.
我一直想改变
无论如何，你的尾灯，加里。
Now there's not
one square inch of dark.
现在没有了
一平方英寸的黑暗。
Meow.
喵。
What was that Gary?
那个加里是什么？
Meow.
喵。
I've got darkness inside of me!
我的内心充满了黑暗！
Hey, SpongeBob's having
a party without me?
嘿，海绵宝宝有
没有我的聚会？
Throw a party without
your best friend,
we'll see about that-augh!
Throw a party without
your best friend,
我们拭目以待吧——噢！
That was close, Patrick.
很接近了，帕特里克。
You're safe here
under these night lights.
你在这里很安全
在这些夜灯下。
But you gotta stay out of
the dark, buddy!
但你必须远离
黑暗，伙计！
You never know what kind
of creeping critter could
be lurking in those shadows.
你永远不知道哪种
爬行动物可以
潜伏在那些阴影中。
Wait, Patrick!
等等，帕特里克！
What is that, Gary?
那是什么，加里？
Patrick, what are you doing?
帕特里克，你在做什么？
Oh, I had to move my rock
out of the dark and into
the light.
哦，我必须移动我的石头
走出黑暗并进入
光。
You know what that means...
你知道这意味着什么...
Sleep over!
睡过去吧！
Your sleeping bag, sir.
你的睡袋，先生。
Thank you, my good man.
谢谢你，我的好人。
oh, Patrick, I'm so glad
you made that gaping hole
in the wall.
哦，帕特里克，我很高兴
你造成了那个大洞
在墙上。
Letting in all the-th-th-th...
让所有的第...
the dark!
黑暗！
Burning, augh!
燃烧啊啊啊！
I can feel it, Pat,
the darkness.
我能感觉到，帕特，
黑暗。
Like it's creeping up on us.
就像它正在向我们蔓延一样。
What are you two
whimpering about?
你们两个是什么
呜咽着什么？
it's me, Squidward, you idiots.
是我，章鱼哥，你们这些白痴。
Hi, Squidward.
嗨，章鱼哥。
Listen, guys.
听着，伙计们。
I don't care or want to know
what you do in your spare time
我不在乎也不想知道
你业余时间做什么
but could you
turn off all these lights?
但你可以吗
关掉所有这些灯？
But Squidward,
without our night lights
但是章鱼哥，
没有我们的夜灯
the creepy creatures
of the dark...
令人毛骨悚然的生物
黑暗的...
Oh, SpongeBob, there are no
"creepy creatures of the dark."
哦，海绵宝宝，没有
“黑暗中令人毛骨悚然的生物。”
It's all in your imagination.
这一切都在你的想象中。
No, Squidward!
不，章鱼哥！
Don't go out in the dark!
天黑的时候不要出去！
Oh, why won't he listen?
哦，他为什么不听？
Patrick, maybe
Squidward's right.
帕特里克，也许
章鱼哥是对的。
What if all this  is
just in our imagination?
如果这一切都是怎么办
只是在我们的想象中吗？
In that case,
we'll need even more lights.
在那种情况下，
我们需要更多的灯。
You said it, Pat.
你说过了，帕特。
Quick, SpongeBob.
快点，海绵宝宝。
Turn it on.
打开它。
More light!
更轻！
Now, SpongeBob!
现在，海绵宝宝！
More light!
更轻！
Man: The battery-operated spoon
has saved me so much time.
男：电池供电的勺子
节省了我很多时间。
This is what passes for
info-tainment these days?
这就是所谓的
现在的信息娱乐？
Sweet mother of
Neptune's mother!
甜蜜的妈妈
海王星的母亲！
Look, Barnacle Boy!
看，藤壶男孩！
A call to action!
号召大家行动起来！
To the invisible boat mobile.
向隐形船移动。
More lights, SpongeBob.
更多灯光，海绵宝宝。
More lights.
更多的灯。
Mermaid Man!
人鱼男！
Barnacle Boy!
藤壶男孩！
Aw, are you guys here
to protect us from the darkness
that surrounds us?
噢，你们在吗？
保护我们免受黑暗的侵害
我们周围的？
We don't have time
for your childish games.
我们没有时间
为了你幼稚的游戏。
We're responding to the distress
signal that you sent.
我们正在应对困境
您发送的信号。
Oh, I'm sorry,
Mermaid Man and Barnacle Boy.
哦，对不起，
美人鱼人和藤壶男孩。
There appears to be
a misunderstanding.
似乎有
一个误会。
You see, Patrick and I put up
all these lights to scare away
the monsters in the dark.
你看，帕特里克和我忍受了
所有这些灯光都吓跑了
黑暗中的怪物。
We weren't trying to summon you.
我们并不是想召唤你。
Oh, fiddlesticks, SpongeBob.
哦，小提琴手，海绵宝宝。
Do you know how hard it is
for us, in our advanced age,
to move?
你知道这有多难吗
对于年事已高的我们来说，
移动？
Don't shine a giant light
in the sky unless there's
a real emergency.
不要发出巨大的光
在天空中除非有
真正的紧急情况。
And another thing...
还有一件事...
What the?
什么？
Dear Neptune!
亲爱的海王星！
It's the most dangerous
and foreboding of all
our arch-nemesis!
这是最危险的
以及一切的预感
我们的宿敌！
My mortal enemy that I have
searched 57 years for!
我的死敌
寻找了57年！
At last I have you!
我终于拥有你了！
Come get some, fiend.
来吧，恶魔。
Come back here, rival!
回来吧，对手！
Oh, my!
哦，天哪！
Mermaid Man needs assistance.
美人鱼人需要帮助。
There's no need to fear,
AbsorboPants is here.
没有必要害怕，
AbsorboPants 在这里。
Savory light.
咸味的光。
Come to me...
到我这里来...
Huh?
啊？
Say, let me help you.
说吧，我来帮你吧。
Is that enough light for you?
这对你来说足够吗？
O.K., guys,
he's all taken care of.
好吧，伙计们，
他都被照顾好了。
Who?
WHO？
世界卫生组织？
The moth, silly.
飞蛾啊，傻啊。
Your arch-enemy.
你的宿敌。
You'll be happy to know
he won't be going anywhere
any time soon.
你会很高兴知道
他不会去任何地方
很快。
See you in  another  57 years.
再过57年再见。
No...!
不...！
I think it's time to go home.
我想是时候回家了。
Why are we here again?
我们怎么又来了？
Bye, Mermaid Man
and Barnacle Boy.
再见，人鱼男
和藤壶男孩。
Who are those two hideous
creatures of the dark?
那两个丑陋的人是谁
黑暗生物？
Oh, I'll tell you about it
in the morning.
哦，我会告诉你这件事
早上。
Now, drive.
现在，开车吧。
We are all alone, Patrick.
我们都很孤独，帕特里克。
No light, no shelter.
没有光，没有庇护所。
Huh?
啊？
Look, SpongeBob.
看，海绵宝宝。
There's a really big light.
确实有一个很大的光。
I'll go get it, buddy.
我去拿它，伙计。
SpongeBob: Pat!
海绵宝宝：帕特！
Come ba...
来吧...
Too much light! Too much light!
光线太多！光线太多！
Patrick:
帕特里克：